[
	{
		"front": "World War I began after the assassination of who?",
		"back": "Arch-Duke Ferdinand"
	},
	{
		"front": "Adolf Hitler was born in the city of Lintz in what country?",
		"back": "Austria"
	},
	{
		"front": "JFK was assassinated while driving through what city in November 1963?",
		"back": "Dallas"
	},
	{
		"front": "Who was the commanding general of the Battle of New Orleans in 1815?",
		"back": "Andrew Jackson"
	},
	{
		"front": "The American involvement in the Korean war lasted from 1950 to what year?",
		"back": "1953"
	},
	{
		"front": "The Battle of Hastings in 1066 was fought in what country?",
		"back": "England"
	},
	{
		"front": "In 1594 Shakespeare became an actor and a playwright in the company of what Theatre?",
		"back": "Globe"
	},
	{
		"front": "The Khmer Rouge was a regime ruling what country of in the 20th century?",
		"back": "Cambodia"
	},
	{
		"front": "Who was the famous 5th century A.D conqueror known as 'The Scourge of God'?",
		"back": "Atilla the Hun"
	},
	{
		"front": "Who was the first Western explorer to reach China?",
		"back": "Marco Polo"
	}
]
